Raj Himanshu

Event Coordinator

Accomplished client-focused wedding coordinator with 2.5 years of experience in project planning and execution. Superb command of consulting with clients to determine objectives and needs for event. Excellent skills at contract negotiations, vendor relationships and day-of-event emergencies.



himanshu.raj73@gmail.com

8507483605 / 7667370576

Near Sanjay Park, House No - H 19 B , Block - H , Gali No - 2, Shakarpur. , Delhi, INDIA

EDUCATION

BCA

Admerit Business College, Patna

04/2013 - 07/2016

Patna,Bihar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Event Coordinator / Event PlannerGuru Raj Trust (Hoonkar)

03/2017 - 03/2018

Patna, Blhar

Tasks

- Managed administrative logistics of events planning, including contract signing, fee collection, event booking and event promotions.
- Selected and ordered decoration and event materials.
- Coordinated schedules and timelines for all events.
- Worked closely with couples to meet wedding goals, maintain deadlines and resolve complaints or service issues.
- Accurately calculated and processed expenses during and after events.
- Supervised helpers and co-workers.
- Arranged equipment, transportation, and other day-ofevent needs.
- Coordinated with participating vendors during event planning.
- Launched social media campaign to promote services.
- Performed face-to-face meetings to finalize contract for services and event details.

Event Manager HR Entertainment

03/2018 - 06/2019

Patna,Bihar

Tasks

- Managed day-to-day business operations, including accounting, finance, HR, marketing and public relations.
- Hired and cross-trained staff members for various eventspecific functions and ensured employees' understanding of associated processes and procedures.
- Created and monitored promotional approaches to increase sales and profit levels.
- Coordinated catering services and planned menus to compliment event theme and selected musical or guest speaker entertainment.
- Oversaw preparation and management of event budgets to deliver at or below projected costs.

SKILLS

Interpersonal Skills	
Time Management Skill	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Creative and innovative	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Flexibility	\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ
Leadership Skill	
Organizational Skill	

PERSONAL PROJECTS

New Year Blast 2019 (11/2018 - 12/2018)

Fight For Light season-1 (01/2019 – 05/2019)

CERTIFICATES

Vocal (05/2014 - Present)

Guitar Playing (06/2015 – Present)

LANGUAGES

HINDI ENGLISH
Full Professional Proficiency Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Events | Singing | Guitar | Acting